manscaped.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy For Manscaped Website - Manscaped.com

**Effective Date:** October 1st, 2017

This website and mobile version and other applications (“Site”) are operated by Manscaped, LLC. This is a legal agreement between you (“You”) and Manscaped, LLC (the “Company” or “we”). We understand that your privacy is important, and we are strongly committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To demonstrate our commitment to you, our customer, we have created this Privacy Policy to explain what information we collect and how we use such information. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using, or submitting information, to this Site. By accessing the Site on any computer, mobile phone, tablet, or other device (collectively, “Device”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on the Site. Your continued use of the Site affirms your agreement to such changes. We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are using the information we collect.

**SECTION 1 – Collection of Personal Information**

Personal Information

We collect personal information from you when you submit it to us, including by (i) placing an order; (ii) registering as a customer; (iii) emailing us; (iv) participating in promotions, surveys, email newsletters or other features of the Site; and (v) communicating or coordinating with a customer service representative. Such personal information may include your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, credit card information and other applicable information.

Non-Personal Information

When you visit the Site, we may collect certain non-personal information from you, including your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the specific web pages visited during your connection, and the domain name from which you accessed the Site. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other clickstream data. We may also use non-personal information for statistical analysis, research, and other purposes.

Like many commercial websites, we analyze how visitors use our Site through what is known as “cookie” technology. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer when you access the Site and allows us to recognize you each time you visit the Site. We may use cookies to: (i) allow you to use the Site without having to re-enter your user name and password; (ii) enhance or personalize your Site usage and shopping experience; (iii) monitor Site usage; (iv) manage the Site; and (v) improve the Site and our products and services. If you choose, you can set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual or all of the cookies on your computer by following your browser’s help file directions. However, if your browser is set to reject cookies or you manually delete cookies, you may have some trouble accessing and using some of the pages and features that are currently on our Site, or that we may put on our Site in the future.

We may also use web beacons on the Site, in our emails and in our advertisements on other websites. Web beacons are tiny graphic images that are used to collect information about your Site visit, such as the pages you view and the features you use, as well as information about whether you open and/or act upon one of our emails or advertisements. We may also collect the URL of the website you visited immediately before coming to the Site. Web beacons help us analyze our Site visitors’ behavior and measure the effectiveness of the Site and our advertising. We may work with service providers, such as Google Analytics, that help us track, collect and analyze this information.

We may combine the non-personal information we collect, such as through cookies and web beacons, with other information we have collected from you.

**SECTION 2 – Use of Information**

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (i) to complete a transaction (including the fulfillment of orders); (ii) to communicate with you regarding your order/s or to notify you about other products and services; (iii) to review Site usage and operations; (iv) to address problems with the Site, our business or our services; (v) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business; (vi) to monitor the Site for compliance with our [Terms of Use](https://www.manscaped.com/pages/terms-conditions "Terms of Use") and the law; and (vii) to contact you with Site updates, newsletters and other informational and promotional materials from us.

If you change your mind and no longer wish to receive these updates, you can opt-out at any time by sending an email to [support@manscaped.com](mailto:support@manscaped.com) or by mail to:

Manscaped

3394 Carmel Mountain Road, Suite 140

San Diego, CA 92121

Please note that even if you opt-out of receiving marketing emails from us, you may still receive email messages regarding your order, such as order confirmation, shipping information, and customer service notifications.

**SECTION 3 – Disclosure**

We may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our related companies and service providers, to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) to our marketing partners, advertisers or other third parties, who may contact you with their own offers; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order) and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (5) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. We may also disclose your personal information with your express consent. We may share aggregate, non-personal information about Site users with third parties.

**SECTION 4 - Security**

We maintain reasonable and appropriate measures designed to maintain information we collect in a secure manner. We have taken certain physical, electronic, and administrative steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Site visitors. Even though we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances.

**SECTION 5 – Your California Privacy Rights**

California law permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:

Manscaped

3394 Carmel Mountain Road, Suite 140

San Diego, CA 92121

**SECTION 6 – Interest Based Advertising**

The Site may include third-party advertising and links to other websites. These third-party websites and advertisers, or internet advertising companies working on their own behalf, sometimes use technology to send, directly to your browser, advertisements that appear on our website. They may also use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect anonymous information in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. To learn more about behavioral advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. Note that electing to opt-out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. In addition, note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

**SECTION 7 – Children**

We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

**SECTION 8 – International Users**

The Site may be accessed by an international audience. By visiting the Site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in this policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction and in jurisdictions, which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.

**SECTION 9 – Third-Party Websites**

This Site may contain links to third-party websites that are not affiliated with the Company, and which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. Once you leave the Site or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you may no longer be governed by this Privacy Policy or the Site’s Terms of Service. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements before disclosing any personal information. Please contact those websites directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

**SECTION 10 – Questions and Contact Information**

If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at: [legal@manscaped.com](mailto:legal@manscaped.com) or by mail at:

Manscaped

3394 Carmel Mountain Road, Suite 140

San Diego, CA 92121

If we need, or are required, to contact you concerning any event that involves your information, we may do so by email, telephone, or mail.
